Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845 - 1993 MSS 057
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence from Charles L. Dodgson
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 4pp The Eagle, Rugby, April 19, 1860 (I 7) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 42)., 0338 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs 11pp [Christ Church, Oxford][December 18, 1860] (I 9)First page missing 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 44)., 0439 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 12pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 20, 1861 (I 10) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 47)., 0343 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 8pp Freshwater, April 19, 1862 (I 12) With 3 pages of manuscript of 8 year old Lionel Tennyson"s poetry. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 53)., 0352 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 8pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 26, 1867 (I 13) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 103)., 0364 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 1p [Doncaster] January 13, 1870 (I 15) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 146)., 0373 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 26, 1870 (I 16) 7 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 147)., 0374 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs 7pp Brodick Hotel, Isle of Arran, September 19, 1871 (I 17) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 165)., 0377 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 30, 1873 (I 18) 6.25 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 199)., 0385 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, June 11, 1884 (I 20) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 543)., 0388 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, November 30, 1888 (I 21) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 724)., 0392 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, May 14, 1889 (I 22) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 740)., 0396 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 4, 1891 (I 23) 5.5 x 7., 0400 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 10, 1892 (I 24) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 915)., 0403 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 21, 1893 (I 25) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 977)., 0408 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 5, 1898 (I 26) 7 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 1155)., 0413 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S. ALs, 2pp [n.p., n.d.] (I 19) Partial letter. Begins "..series from 1851 7 x 4.5., undated; 0451 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Stuart ALs, 7pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 29, 1891 (I 29) 8.5 x 12 (Cohen pg. #: 877)., 0454 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collingwood, Stuart ALs, 4pp [n.p.] January 5, 1898 (I 27) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1155)., 0462 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, May 28, 1875 (XIV 221) 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 226)., 0467 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 6, 1890 (XIV 222) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 793)., 0472 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 9, 1890 (XIV 223) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 794)., 0476 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 5pp. 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 9, 1890 (XIV 224) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 796)., 0480 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 12, 1890 (XIV 225) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 797)., 0486 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, August 28, 1890 (XIV 226) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 802)., 0490 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 19, 1891 (XIV 229) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 851)., 0495 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 28, 1891 (XIV 228) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 853)., 0500 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 4, 1891 (XIV 227) 5.5 x 7., 0504 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 15, 1891 (XIV 230) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 872)., 0508 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Collins, R.H. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 7, 1893 (XIV 231) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 969)., 0512 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Commins, [?] ACs 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 11, 1894 (331) Removed from 1st English ed.(1866) of Alice. LCN=11870297. (Box 1, Folder ID: 108.1)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Cunnynghame, Margaret ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 30, 1868 (II 35) See drawings 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 112)., 0516 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Cunnynghame, Margaret AL, 4pp United Hotel, Charles Street, Haymarket, April 7, 1868 (II 34) Signature has been cut from letter 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 115)., 0521 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Daniel, Mrs. C.H.O ACs, 1p Christ Church, March 18, 1895 (XIX 565) 3 x 4.75., 0526 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Denman, George ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, July 12, 1873 This letter, originally laid in with the Edith Denman copy of The Hunting of the Snark, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 190)., 0529 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Denman, George ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 6, 1876 This letter, originally laid in with the Edith Denman copy of The Hunting of the Snark, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 246)., 0533 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Henrietta To Dodgson, Edwin Heron ALs, illus, 4pp [Christ Church, Oxford] January 31, [1855] (XIX 455) 8 x 10 (Cohen pg. #: 31)., 0538 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Edwin Heron ALs, 16pp Christ Church, March 11, 1867 (XIX 456) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 99)., 0543 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Edwin Heron ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 18, 1890 (XIX 457) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 776)., 0560 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Elisabeth, "Lizzie" ALs, 12pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 25, 1894 (XIX 558) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1040)., 0578 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Elisabeth, "Lizzie" ALs, 8pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 29, 1894 (XVII 296) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1043)., 0565 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Louisa ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 21, 1897 (XIX 562) 4.5 x 7., 0587 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - For Dodgson, Charles to Dodgson, Mary see Dodgson, Charles to Collingwood, Mrs. C.E.S., n/a (Box 2)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dodgson, Wilfred ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 30, 1887 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 675)., 0599 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Draper, Dorothy, "Dolly". PLs, 1p 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 21, 1885 No number. Circular letter re: finding a tenant 7 x 4.5., 0601 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - For Charles Dodgson to Drury, Mary see Charles Dodgson to Fuller, Mrs. H.H., n/a (Box 2)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Drury, Mrs. J.S. ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, August 8, 1869 (XIX 460) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 134)., 0602 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Dyer, Mrs. B. ALs, 3pp. Christ Church, Oxford, April 6, 1887 (XIX 509) Cyclostyle 8 x 4.75., 0606 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Earle, Beatrice ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 3, 1884 (XIX 502) 6.25 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 529)., 0610 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Feilden, Helen ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 1, 1879 (XIX 464) 7 x 8.75 (Cohen pg. #: 328)., 0615 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Feilden, Helen ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, December 31, 1879 (XIX 465) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 361)., 0620 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Feilden, Mrs. H.A. ALs, 7pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 16, 1880 (XIX 480) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 377)., 0629 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Feilden, Mrs. H.A. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, Thursday, [November 9, 1882] (XIX 482) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 468)., 0625 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Feilden, Mrs. H.A. ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 12, 1887 (XIX 481) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 662)., 0637 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ffoulkes, Mrs. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 29, 1880 (XIX 472) See picture file for photo #2644. With envelope 6 x 4., 0642 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Fletcher, K.R. ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, November 20, 1889 (XIX 497) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 764)., 0645 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Fletcher, K. R. ALs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, July 1, 1890 (XIX 498) 4 x 6.25., 0649 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Franklin, Mrs. ALs, 3pp [Christ Church, Oxford] October 18, 1865 (XIX 454) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 79)., 0650 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Fuller, Mrs. H.H. ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, June 7, 1883 (XIX 500) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 496)., 0753 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Furniss, Harry ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 17, 1889 (XIX 530) 6 x 8., 0654 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Furniss, Harry AD, 1p [n.p., n.d.] (XIX 531) Partial. One leaf numbered "5". 4.5 x 9., undated; 0658 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Dodgson, Charles To W. George"s Sons AN, 1p Christ Church Oxford, November 7, 1890 (XIX 532) Docketed on verso by G.H. During. 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 811)., 0659 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Girdlestone, Robert ALs, 2pp Christ Church Oxford, March 8, 1880 (XIX 485) 5.25 x 6.75., 0665 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Girdlestone, Robert Als, 2pp Christ Church Oxford, November 7, 1886 (XIX 483) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 646)., 0662 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Girdlestone, Robert ALs, 3pp [7 Lushington Road], Eastbourne, October 8, 1889 (XIX 486) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 759)., 0668 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Girdlestone, Mrs. R. ALs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, February 17, [n.d.] (XIX 484) 6.25 x 7.75., undated; 0672 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Harcourt, Mr. A.G.V. ALs, 1p [n.p., n.d.] (XIX 488) 4.75 x 8., undated; 0673 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hardman, Frances ALs, illus, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 6, 1881 (XIX 489) Contains the "Puzzle of the Three Bridges". 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 445)., 0674 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hargreaves, Mrs. R.G. ALs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, March 21, 1885 (IX 127) With envelope. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 568)., 0677 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hargreaves, Mrs. R.G. ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, July 15, 1885 (IX 128) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 588)., 0678 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hargreaves, Mrs. R.G. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 14, 1885 (IX 129) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 597)., 0682 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hargreaves, Mrs. R.G. ALs, 1p 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 23, 1885 (IX 130) With envelope. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 603)., 0686 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hargreaves, Mrs. R.G. ALs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, November 6, 1886 (IX 131) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 646)., 0687 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Harvey, H.A. ALs, 3pp [n.p.] March 2, [1877] (XIX 537) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 271)., 0868 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hatch, Beatrice ALs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, January 30, 1894 (323) With envelope. 3.5 x 5.25., 0688 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hatch, Beatrice ALs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, July 21, 1894 (324) With envelope. 3.5 x 5.25., 0689 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hatch, Beatrice ACs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, December 7, 1894 (325) With envelope. 3.5 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 1046)., 0690 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hatch, Beatrice ALs,1p 2 Bedford Well Road, Eastbourne, September 6, 1896 (326) 4.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 1098)., 0691 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hatch, Beatrice ALs, 2pp Christ Church Oxford, December 17, 1897 (327) With envelope. 3.75 x 6 (Cohen pg. #: 1153)., 0692 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hatch, Beatrice AD, 1p [n.p.], February 14, [n.y.] (340) Note to "Emily," perhaps Hatch"s doll, from "Mabel.". 7 x 4.25., undated; 0695 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hill, Mrs. C.F. ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 13, 1886 (XIX 505) 7 x 4.25 (Cohen pg. #: 617)., 0745 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hill, Mrs. C.F. ALs, 4pp Christ Church Oxford, June 17, 1897 (XIX 506) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1128)., 0748 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hill, Mrs. C.F. ALs, 3pp [n.p.] Wednesday, [n.d.] (XIX 501) 5.25 x 6.75., undated; 0757 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Holiday, Winifred ALs, 4pp Christ Church Oxford, February 28, 1889 (XIX 524) With envelope.. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 729)., 0698 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Holiday, Winifred ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, May 26, 1892 (XIX 525) With envelope. 5.5 x 7., 0703 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Agnes ALs, illus, 4pp Christ Church Oxford, June 22, 1870 This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. 7 x 9., 0711 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Agnes ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, March 26, 1871 This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. 5.25 x 6.75., 0726 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Agnes ALs, 4pp [n.p., n.d.] This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. 5.25 x 7., undated; 0729 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Amy ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, December 1, 1867 This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. 5.25 x 7., 0707 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Amy ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 2, 1871 This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. 7 x 9., 0713 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Amy ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, February 24, 1871 This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. 7 x 9., 0718 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Amy ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, April 4, 1871 This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1997 and placed with the letters in the collection. Includes a poem. 7 x 9., 0723 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hughes, Amy and Agnes ALs, illus, 3pp [m.p., n.d.] This letter, originally laid in with the Agnes Hughes copy of Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland, was removed from that copy in October of 1987 and placed with the letters in the collection. 7 x 4.5., undated; 0734 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hunter, Mrs. W. ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, November 27, 1888 (XIX 507) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 721)., 0738 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Hunter, Mrs. W. ALs, 2pp Christ Church Oxford, November 29, 1888 (XIX 508) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 722)., 0742 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - For Dodgson, Charles to Hussey, Elizabeth see Dodgson, Charles to Hill, Mrs. C.F.., n/a (Box 2)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Jackson, Florence ALs, 1p 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 21 1890 (XIX 533) Miniature letter in stamp case. 1 x 1.5 (Cohen pg. #: 809)., undated; 0761 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Jebb, Edith ALs, 2pp [n.p. n.d.] (XIX 461) 4 x 5.5., undated; 0766 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Kish, Thomas ANs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, March 21, 1882 (XIX 492) Docketed on verso. 5 x 5., 0769 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Kish, Thomas ANs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, November 14, 1883 (XIX 493) Docketed on verso. 3.25 x 5.5., 0772 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Kish, Thomas ANs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, March 21, 1882 (XIX 494) Docketed on verso. 3.5 x 5., 0775 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Kish, Thomas ANs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, December 21, 1883 (XIX 495) Docketed on verso. 7 x 4.5., 0778 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Kish, Thomas ANs, 1p Christ Church Oxford, February 19, 1889 (XIX 496) Docketed on verso. 4.25 x 7., 0781 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Kitchin, Alexandra ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, May 26, 1892 (III 39) 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 903)., 0784 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Knight, Ellen, "Nellie" TL, 1p c/o Messrs. Macmillan, 29 Bedford Street, Covent Garden, August 28, 1888 (XIX 517) 7 x 4.25 (Cohen pg. #: 716)., 0788 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Knight, Ellen, "Nellie" ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 1, 1888 (XIX 518) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 717)., 0789 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Knight, Ellen, "Nellie" ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 18, 1888 (XIX 519) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 718)., 0794 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Knight, Ellen, "Nellie" n.p. [August 6, 1891] Envelope (1) (XIX 519a). (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Langbridge, Gladys ALs, 4pp Christ Church Oxford, June 26, 1897 (XIX 561) 8.75 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1129)., 0799 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Langbridge, Frederick ALs, 2pp Christ Church Oxford, November 13, 1896 (XIX 559) 4.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1103)., 0804 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Langbridge, Frederick ALs, 2pp Christ Church Oxford December 3, 1896 (XIX 560) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1108)., 0807 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Laverty, W.H. ALs, 3pp Christ Church Oxford, March 28, 1878 (X 145) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 303)., 0810 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Laverty, W.H. ALs, 4pp Christ Church Oxford, April 2, 1878 (X 146) 7 x 9., 0814 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Laverty, W.H. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 19, 1882 (X 147) 7 x 9., 0819 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Leopold, Prince, Duke of Albany ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 31, 1876 (XIX 471) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 240)., 0823 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - For Dodgson, Charles to Liddell, Alice see Dodgson, Charles to Hargreaves, Mrs. R.G.., n/a (Box 2)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Liddell, Mrs. H.G. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, Sunday Night, [n.d.] (XIX 549) 5.5 x 7., undated; 0828 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Liddell, Mrs. H.G. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 2, 1893 (XIX 550) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 944)., 0831 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Letchworth, Mr. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, May 21, 1880 (XIX 487) 5.25 x 6.75., 0835 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Lucy, Edith ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 19, 1890 (XIX 534) With envelope. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 798)., 0836 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Lucy, Edith Envelope (1) [Christ Church] Oxford, July 13, 1893 (XIX 551+552). (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Lucy, Edith ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, November 26, 1893 (XIX 535) With envelope.. 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 996)., 0841 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Mallalieu, William ALs, 5pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 17, 1892 (XIX 545) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 918)., 0855 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Mallalieu, Mrs. W. ALs, 6pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 19, 1892 (XIX 546) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 920)., 0861 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Mallalieu, Mrs. W. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, July 8, 1892 (XIX 543)Third page small envelope. 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 914)., 0846 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Mallalieu, Mrs. W. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 11, 1892 (XIX 544) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 916)., 0850 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Mallalieu Envelopes (2) [Christ Church], Oxford, July 29, 1892 (XIX 547a) [7 Lushington Road] Eastbourne, September 7, 1892 (XIX 547) (Cohen pg. #: 927). (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Martin-Harvey, Mrs. J. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 30, 1895 (XIX 538) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1064)., 0872 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Nicholson, E.W.B. ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 19, 1893 (XIX 553) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 976)., 0875 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Potts, Mr. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, April 14, 1883 (322) 5.25 x 6.75., 0879 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Rivers, H.F. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 10, 1874 (XIX 462) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 209)., 0880 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Rivers, H.F. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 19, 1874 (XIX 463) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 210)., 0884 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Rix, Edith AC, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, June 8, 1891 (XIX 540) 3 x 4.75., 0888 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - For Dodgson, Charles to Sadler, Michael see Dodgson, Charles to Steward, Christ Church.., n/a (Box 2)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 5pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 30, 1886 (350) Cyclostyle. 8 x 4.75 (Cohen pg. #: 636)., 0891 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 2, 1886 (358) 6.25 x 7.75., 0897 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 6, 1886 (359) 6.25 x 7.75., 0902 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 7, 1886 (360) 6.25 x 7.75., 0906 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 14, 1886 (361) 6.25 x 7.75., 0911 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 6pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 17, 1886 (351) Cyclostyle. 8.25 x 4.75., 0912 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 24, 1886 (362) 6.25 x 7.75., 0919 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 28, 1886 (370) 6.25 x 7.75., 0922 (Box 3, Folder 214)